Guide to the William Sloane Coffin, Jr. Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1918-1996; Accession 2004-M-009
  - Writings
    - Speeches
      - "Lecture No. 1," "Lecture 2," and "Lecture 3" [unknown connection], Undated (Box 29, Folder 724)
      - [Marriage ceremony of "Catherine and Ralph"], Undated (Box 29, Folder 725)
      - "Personal Journey to Peace-to X + to Peace" [notes probably for speech], Undated (Box 29, Folder 726)
      - "Report to the Board" [of SANE/FREEZE], Undated (Box 29, Folder 727)
      - "So We Do Not Lose Heart"
      - "To My Fellow Clergy", Undated (Box 29, Folder 728)
      - Untitled [on Reverse the Arms Race], Undated (Box 29, Folder 729)
      - "SANE/FREEZE Fund-Raiser Nashville" [notes probably for speech], Undated (Box 29, Folder 730)
      - "UCC Synod" [notes probably for speech], Undated (Box 29, Folder 731)
      - Untitled, [SANE/FREEZE], Undated (Box 29, Folder 732)
      - Miscellaneous [unidentified speeches, notes for speeches, portions of speeches], Undated (Box 29, Folder 733 - 737)
    - Writings by others
      - Books
        - Jeremias, Joachim, Rediscovering the Parables, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 738)
        - Wilkinson, T. H., Brown to Bakke, pp. 262-297, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 739)
        - Unknown author, Toward a Revolution in the USSR, 1957 spring (Box 29, Folder 740)
      - Essays and articles
        - Alperovitz, Gar and Jeff Faux, "An Economic Program for the Coming Decade" [with correspondence], 1975 October 29, undated (Box 29, Folder 741)
        - Bonino, José Míguez, "Theology and Liberation", 1971 (Box 29, Folder 742)
        - Chomsky, Noam, untitled, Undated (Box 29, Folder 743)
        - Diamond, John, untitled for Yale Daily News supplemental magazine, 1969 October (Box 29, Folder 744)
        - Dumas, Andre, "Whether These Were Sins, Not Simply Mistakes", Undated (Box 29, Folder 745)
        - Everett, Robert, "James Parkes and the Quest for a Christian Theology without Antisemitism", Undated (Box 29, Folder 746)
        - Gall, Donald A., "Down...Down on the Farm", Undated (Box 29, Folder 747)
        - Gillan, Ann, "International Dimensions of Antisemitism", Undated (Box 29, Folder 748)
        - Habib, Gabriel, "Middle East: A Crisis for Faith and the Church", 1991 August (Box 29, Folder 749)
        - Horton, Marjorie, "The Disarmament Program of the Riverside Church" [and related materials], [1988?] (Box 29, Folder 750)
        - Iiams, Thomas Marion, "Dissent and Job Security on an Alabama Campus" [abstract and a portion], Undated (Box 30, Folder 751)
        - Jacob, Philip E., "A Profile of the Values of American College Students" [reprint], 1957 (Box 30, Folder 752)
        - Kaufman, Gordon D., "Reconceiving God for a Nuclear Age", 1985 (Box 30, Folder 753)
        - Klare, Michael T., "Bloodbath in the Making....It Looks Like War", [1990] (Box 30, Folder 754)
        - Kolko, Gabriel, untitled, Undated (Box 30, Folder 755)
        - Landau, Saul, various writings, 1992, undated (Box 30, Folder 756)
        - Loury, Glenn C., "Beyond Civil Rights", 1985 October 7 (Box 30, Folder 757)
        - Mack, John E., various writings, 1982-1989 (Box 30, Folder 758 - 759)
        - Maguire, John, [on psychotherapy and religion], Undated (Box 30, Folder 760)
        - N. G. D., "Nucl Wah", 1978 February 12 (Box 30, Folder 761)
        - Peccei, Aurelio, "The Humanistic Revolution" [with correspondence], 1975 Jan, Sep, November 6 (Box 30, Folder 762)
        - Rampilla, Narayana Rao, "Philosophical Contours of Civil Disobedience...", Undated (Box 30, Folder 763)
        - Roblee, Frederick A., "Affirming the Future", 1987, undated (Box 30, Folder 764)
        - Sewall, Richard, [review of Once to Every Man ], Undated (Box 30, Folder 765)
        - Shishkov, Yuri, "The Costs of the Arms Race", 1989 (Box 30, Folder 766)
        - Shoemaker, Samuel M., "The Lent God Wills", Undated (Box 30, Folder 767)
        - Steffen, Lloyd, "Why this Waste" [incomplete], Undated (Box 30, Folder 768)
        - Stevenson, Edward, various writings, 1988, undated (Box 30, Folder 769)
        - Washington, James, "The Grace of Interruptions: Towards a New Vision of Christian History", 1987, undated (Box 30, Folder 770)
        - Weiss, Cora, "Women for a Meaningful Summit...", 1989 June 1-6 (Box 30, Folder 771)
        - West, Cornel
          - "Ethics and Action in Frederic Jameson's Marxist Hermeneutics", 1986 (Box 30, Folder 772)
          - "The Historicist Turn in Philosophy of Religion", 1985 (Box 30, Folder 773)
        - Wheatley, Melvin, "A Bishop's Statement on Homosexuality", 1981 October 12 (Box 30, Folder 774)
        - Yanov, Alex, "Dear Mr. President" [and related materials], 1989 (Box 30, Folder 775 - 777)
        - Various or unknown writers
          - [Papers submitted for Coffin's course at Vanderbilt Divinity School], 1992 April (Box 30, Folder 778)
          - "Prayers for Peace in the Middle East", 1990 August (Box 30, Folder 779)
          - "Welcome O Life! I Go to Encounter for the Millionth Time" [prospectus for a documentary film about WSC], Undated (Box 30, Folder 780)
        - Miscellaneous, 1983, 1988-1989, undated (Box 30, Folder 781)
      - Sermons
        - Yale: Battell [unless otherwise noted]
          - Carter, Sallie, untitled [Yale Divinity School chapel], 1975 November 4 (Box 31, Folder 782)
          - Loder, Theodore W., untitled, 1967 October 1 (Box 31, Folder 783)
          - Napier, B. Davie, untitled, 1964 October 25 (Box 31, Folder 784)
          - Neuhaus, Richard, untitled, 1967 October 15 (Box 31, Folder 785)
          - Sittler, J., untitled, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 786)
          - Slie, Samuel Nathaniel
            - "Repentence and Change-Law and Order", 1968 December 1 (Box 31, Folder 787)
            - Untitled, 1975 April 27 (Box 31, Folder 788)
        - Riverside
          - Brown, Brian, "This is a Lighthouse", 1983 September 4 (Box 31, Folder 789)
          - De Jong, Patricia E.
            - "In Search of Minor Miracles", 1984 November 25 (Box 31, Folder 790)
            - "Uprisings of Love", 1986 April 6 (Box 31, Folder 791)
            - "A New Humanity", 1986 June 8 (Box 31, Folder 792)
            - "Being Built Together", 1986 September 14 (Box 31, Folder 793)
          - Laubach, Eugene E.
            - "Feast of the Epiphany", 1980 January 6 (Box 31, Folder 794)
            - "Agenda for the Eighties", 1980 April 20 (Box 31, Folder 795)
            - "A Delicate Balance", 1980 August 10 (Box 31, Folder 796)
            - "The Lonely Place", 1980 November 30 (Box 31, Folder 797)
            - "The Boy Who Wasn't Even Counted", 1981 November 22 (Box 31, Folder 798)
            - "The Greatest Assurance of All", 1985 April 14 (Box 31, Folder 799)
            - "Crust into Butter", 1985 May 19 (Box 31, Folder 800)
            - "Didn't Know Who You Was", 1985 December 29 (Box 31, Folder 801)
            - "The Sacred Journey", 1986 March 16 (Box 31, Folder 802)
            - "He Taught Them to Pray", 1986 June 1 (Box 31, Folder 803)
            - "The Way We Were", 1986 June 29 (Box 31, Folder 804)
          - McCracken, Robert J.
            - "The Dogma of the Assumption of Mary", 1950 November (Box 31, Folder 805)
            - "Mary the Mother of our Lord", 1965 (Box 31, Folder 806)
          - Morikawa, Jitsuo, "Church for Others", 1977 January 9 (Box 31, Folder 807)
          - Newman, Evelyn
            - "A Talent for Caring", 1978 November 12 (Box 31, Folder 808)
            - "Be Born in Us this Day", 1978 December 31 (Box 31, Folder 809)
          - Phillips, Channing E.
            - "Remembering Martin Luther King, Jr.", 1983 January 16 (Box 31, Folder 810)
            - "To See or Not to See", 1984 November 4 (Box 31, Folder 811)
            - "Words from a Black Christian", 1986 February 9 (Box 31, Folder 812)
          - Thomas, George
            - "Makethe Word Flesh", 1978 August 27 (Box 31, Folder 813)
            - "My God, My God...Why?", 1980 May 4 (Box 31, Folder 814)
            - "What is God Like?", 1980 June 29 (Box 31, Folder 815)
            - "God Comes in an Unexpected Way", 1980 August 24 (Box 31, Folder 816)
        - Other locations/location unknown
          - Ferris, Theodore, "On Being Christian in a Mixed Up World", 1961 June 25 (Box 31, Folder 817)
          - Hartt, J. N., "Apocalypse and Covenant", 1971 February 8 (Box 31, Folder 818)
          - Muehl, William
            - Untitled, 1967 February 12 (Box 31, Folder 819)
            - Untitled, 1967 February 19 (Box 31, Folder 820)
          - Myers, C. Kilmer, "The Papacy and Christian Union" [Grace Cathedral, San Francisco, California], 1967 June 4 (Box 31, Folder 821)
          - Napier, B. Davie, "The University and the Person", 1967 April 9 (Box 31, Folder 822)
          - Song, C. S., "People of Galilee, WHY STAND THERE LOOKING UP INTO THE SKY?" [Pacific School of Religion Chapel], 1993 May 18 (Box 31, Folder 823)
          - Stringfellow, William, "The Criminality of Jesus", 1969 October 19 (Box 31, Folder 824)
          - Winn, Albert C., "Tithing is More than the Number Ten" [with related correspondence], 1987, undated (Box 31, Folder 825)
          - No author
            - "Hope for a Season of Mourning", [1991?] (Box 31, Folder 826)
            - "Words in the Sand (A Layperson's Topical Sermon on Capital Punishment)", Undated (Box 31, Folder 827)
      - Speeches
        - Atwood, Christopher, "Statement...on the Current Genocide in the Former Yugoslavia", 1993 March 19 (Box 31, Folder 828)
        - Berrigan, Philip, "The Christian Conscience and War" [at Boston University], 1965 October 1 (Box 31, Folder 829)
        - Clement, Charlie, "Dr. Charlie Clement-Remarks", 1983 May 29 (Box 31, Folder 830)
        - Coffin, Henry, "What the Members Make of the Church", 1937 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 831)
        - Fraser, Don, "Human Rights in the US-USSR Relations" [in Minneapolis, Minnesota-with related materials], 1983 May (Box 31, Folder 832)
        - Goldburg, Robert E., "Thanksgiving Address" [at Woolsey Hall], 1975 November 30 (Box 31, Folder 833)
        - Hester, James M., "To Illuminate Tomorrow", 1975 October 9 (Box 31, Folder 834)
        - Honey, Martha, untitled, Undated (October 16) (Box 31, Folder 835)
          See: Accession 2004-M-009, 1918-1996 Folder 838
        - Kinnamon, Michael, "Address to the General Board of the Christian Church (Disciples of Christ)", 1991 July 27 (Box 31, Folder 836)
        - [Lovett, Sidney], untitled [delivered at Coffin's farewell dinner], [1975 December 11] (Box 31, Folder 837)
        - McGehee, Ralph, untitled, Undated (October 16) (Box 31, Folder 838)
          See also: Accession 2004-M-009, 1918-1996 Folder 835
        - Maguire, John David, "God is Personal: If's, And's, and But's" [at Antioch College], 1959 January 13 (Box 31, Folder 839)
        - Palme, Olof, "The United Nations at Forty" [with introduction by Coffin], 1985 October 20 (Box 31, Folder 840)
        - Papandreou, Margarita, "Speech at the Unveiling of a Statue of Peace" [in Moscow], 1988 May 30 (Box 31, Folder 841)
        - Rasmussen, Larry, "Reformation: A Bad Idea Whose Time is Come" [at Union Theological Seminary], 1987 November 3 (Box 31, Folder 842)
        - Reeves, Paul, "The Search for Peace in an Emerging World Order", 1991 September 11 (Box 31, Folder 843)
        - Sagan, Eli?, "Cultural Diversity and Moral Relativism", Undated (Box 31, Folder 844)
        - Sewall, Richard, "My Dear Hero" [at Coffin's farewell dinner], 1975 December 11 (Box 31, Folder 845)
        - Sheehan, Neil, "Vietnam: How Could this War Have Happened?", 1989 November 20 (Box 31, Folder 846)
        - Tully, S. Peggy, "A Common Denominator in Jesuit Institutions", [1993?] (Box 31, Folder 847)
- Additional Material, 1916-2003; Accession 2004-M-056
  This accession is arranged in seven sections: Correspondence; Personal and family; Printed materials and clippings; Topical; Writings; Audiotapes; and Videotapes. There is also a small amount of oversize material. The materials supplement the previous accessions by documenting Coffin's "semi-retirement" during the 1990s and 2000s and by providing materials about his personal life as a father, son, friend, and minister, during the 1930s through the 1980s.
  Correspondence is divided into three sections: general, family, and geographical. General correspondence is arranged alphabetically and is both personal and professional in nature. It primarily dates to either Coffin's time in the army or the 1990s and 2000s. The section includes correspondence with William F. Buckley, Jr., George Bailey, Manya Piskounoff, Elaine Manson, Bill Moyers, Michael Ferber, and particularly touching sympathy cards from Ted Kennedy and Lou Pollak. Following the general correspondence is a section of correspondence from or to relatives of Coffin, which chiefly date to World War II or the CIA years, with an additional letter from 1983. The majority of the family correspondence consists of the very personal letters to or from Coffin's mother, Catherine Butterfield Coffin. The largest part of the correspondence section is arranged by geographic locality and dates almost entirely to the 1990s and 2000s. Correspondence in the geographical organization is primarily public opinion mail or letters regarding speaking engagements, with a small amount of other personal material. This material was transferred from Coffin's assistant and its original order has, for the most part, been maintained.
  Personal and family is subdivided between materials about William Sloane Coffin, Jr., William Sloane Coffin, Sr. (Coffin's father), and Catherine Butterfield Coffin (Coffin's mother). The William Sloane Coffin, Jr. documents are from his youth, 1946, and 1983. Materials from Coffin's youth include drawings, report cards, medical reports, and a homemade serial created by the Coffin children while living in Carmel-by-the-Sea, California. The 1946 document is Coffin's translation into Russian of Bernard Pares' History of Russia, which Coffin used as a means to learn the language. The material from 1983 consists primarily of notes of condolence following the death of Coffin's son, Alexander, who died in a car accident on January 11, 1983. There are also twenty-six photographs in this section. Photographs are mostly unidentified and undated, though a few seem to date to the 1940s, one to 1972, and the rest to the mid 1980s and later. Many are low quality, home photographs. The identified photographs include pictures of Coffin with Andy Harris (Pacific School of Religion) and Cathy Thaler (Mayor); Gregory Sloane Coffin; Eric Gabriel Coffin; Coffin and his wife, Randy, with Bruce Brackenridge; Coffin at Peace Week at Western Michigan University; Coffin at Sun City; and Coffin at an event about Nicaragua. The photograph from 1972 is from Coffin's trip to Hanoi. Included in the picture are David Dellinger, Cora Weiss, and Richard Falk, as well as three unidentified individuals.
  The William Sloane Coffin, Sr. materials consist of a biography by his wife, Catherine Butterfield Coffin, some writings, and a passport. The materials date to World War I and the 1930s. The Catherine Butterfield Coffin materials include a small amount of correspondence regarding her death in December, 1982. They also include documents regarding the neutrality of Switzerland, where members of the Coffin family were living at the beginning of World War II. Additionally, there is a collection of letters and diary entries, dating to 1918, but apparently typed at a much later date.
  Topical files consist of correspondence, clippings, writings, and other materials on particular subjects and are arranged alphabetically by subject. Topics found in this accession mainly date to Coffin's years at Riverside and later. The one major exception is the large amount of World War II military materials from Coffin's training to become an officer in the United States Army. Other topics of interest include Central America, homosexuality, and sanctuary. Materials relating to Christianity and Crisis generally refer to Coffin's membership on the board of directors.
  Writings supplement similar sections in the previous accessions by adding materials from Coffin's later years. The section is divided into four subsections: essays and short articles, prayers, speeches, and writings by others. Essays and short articles are arranged alphabetically by title and consist mainly of writings for periodicals. The accession contains a very small amount of prayers, found in one folder. Speeches are arranged chronologically and include sermons. Many are from lectures delivered across the country and almost all date to the 1990s or later. Writings by others are divided into essays and short articles and speeches. They are arranged alphabetically by last name.
  The accession includes some sixty, chronologically-arranged audiotapes. They are divided into two subsections based on whether or not Coffin is a primary speaker. A large number are recordings of sermons delivered at Riverside Church and where possible, a cross reference to the written sermon has been included. Other recordings are of interviews of Coffin or speeches by Coffin.
  Videotapes are arranged chronologically and cover a wide variety of topics. Specific information about individual content and quality has been noted in bracket statements.
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - A-S, 1918-2003, undated (Box 1, Folder 1 - 12)
      - T-Z, unidentified, 1918, 1943-1945, 1982-2003, undated (Box 2, Folder 13 - 17)
      - Bailey, George, 1947, 1949, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Bennett, John [1 letter], 1987 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Buckley, William F., Jr. [mainly outgoing, 2 incoming letters], 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Chavchavadze, David, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Clark, Ramsey [1 sympathy letter], 1983 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Comstock, Gary [1 letter], 1991 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Darling, Arthur [1 letter], 1943 July 5 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Falwell, Jerry and Macel [1 sympathy letter], 1983 January 13 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Ferber, Michael, 1997, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Ferm, Anders [1 letter], 1987 July (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Forbes, Jim, 1993-2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Guirey, Chingis [1 letter], 1944 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Harris, Jean, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Kennedy, Edward [1 sympathy letter], 1983 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Leahy, Patrick [1 letter], 1997 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - McGovern, George [1 letter], 1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Manson, Elaine [including 1 photograph], 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Moore, Paul [1 letter], 1987 July 30 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Moyers, Bill, 1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Piskounoff, Manya, 1945-1955, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Pollak, Lou and Kathy [2 sympathy letters], 1983 January (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Raskin, Marcus [1 sympathy letter], 1983 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Rogers, Fred M. [1 sympathy letter], 1983 January 12 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Russell, Valerie, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Shriver, Donald, 1983, 1987, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Sowell, Jeannette and mother, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Throckmorton, Burton, Jr. [1 letter], 1987 August 4 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Trible, Phyllis [1 letter], 1993 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Trudeau, Garry [1 letter], 1989 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Tutu, Desmond [1 letter], 1989 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Wallis, Jim [1 sympathy letter], 1983 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Weiss, Cora, 1988, 1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Wofford, Harris [1 letter], 1992 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Coffin to many recipients, 1990, 1993, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Family
      - Bacon, Carter Smith (cousin?), 1944, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Bacon, Margaret (aunt), 1943, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Coffin, Catherine Butterfield (mother)
        - Incoming, 1943, 1944, undated (Box 3, Folder 54 - 57)
        - Outgoing, 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Coffin, David D. (cousin), 1983 April 16 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Coffin, Henry Sloane (uncle), 1944, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Coffin, Margot (sister) [includes Catherine Butterfield Coffin correspondence], 1943-1944, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Coffin, Ned (brother) [includes photographs and correspondence to other recipients], 1943-1944, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Coffin, William Sloane, Sr. (father) to Euphemia (Sloane) Coffin (grandmother), 1918 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Geographical
      - Alabama-Arkansas, 1990-2001, undated (Box 3, Folder 64 - 67)
      - California-Indiana, 1990-2002, undated (Box 4, Folder 68 - 81)
      - Iowa-Minnesota, 1990-2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 82 - 95)
      - Nebraska-New York, 1990-2003, undated (Box 6, Folder 96 - 110)
      - North Carolina-South Carolina, 1990-2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 111 - 122)
      - Tennessee-Wyoming, 1990-2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 123 - 135)
      - International
        - General, 1992, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 136)
        - Canada, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Personal and family
    - Coffin, William Sloane, Jr.
      - Alex's death
        - Clippings, 1983 Jan, March (Box 9, Folder 138)
        - Correspondence
          - Notes of condolence, 1983 January-March (Box 9, Folder 139 - 146)
          - Notes of condolence, 1983 January-March (Box 10, Folder 147 - 153)
          - Notes of condolence, 1983 January-March (Box 11, Folder 154 - 157)
          - Notes of condolence and other, 1983 April-1984 (Box 11, Folder 158)
          - Regarding sermon, "Alex's Death" its republication [republished as "My Son Beat Me to the Grave"], 1983 January-1984 November (Box 11, Folder 159)
            See also: Accession 2004-M-009, 1918-1996 Folder 510
        - Funeral and memorial services, 1983 Jan, March (Box 11, Folder 160)
        - Writings, 1983, undated (Box 11, Folder 161)
      - Biographical information, Undated (Box 11, Folder 162)
      - Carmel years
        - "Carmel Mission Play", 1935 September 1 (Box 11, Folder 163)
        - "Carmel Sunrise", 1935 (Box 11, Folder 164)
        - Drawings, Undated (Box 11, Folder 165)
        - "The Pacific Quarterly", 1936 Apr, July (Box 11, Folder 166)
        - Schoolwork of Ned and Margot Coffin, [1935]-1937 (Box 11, Folder 167)
      - New York years
        - "Family Memorabilia", 1933, undated (Box 12, Folder 168)
        - Medical reports, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 169)
        - Report cards: Buckley School, 1931-1933 (Box 12, Folder 170)
      - Photographs [26], [1972], 1986-1990, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 171)
      - Russian study book [including notes on history and peoples of the U.S.S.R. and correspondence], [1946], 1951 (Box 12, Folder 172 - 176)
    - Coffin, Catherine Butterfield
      - Death, 1982 December-1983 January (Box 12, Folder 177)
      - Swiss neutrality, 1939-1940, undated (Box 12, Folder 178)
      - World War I diary and correspondence, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 179)
    - Coffin, William Sloane, Sr.
      - Biography [by Catherine Butterfield Coffin-revised, c. 1964], 1935 January 15 (Box 12, Folder 180)
      - Writings and speeches, 1916, 1918, 1933, undated (Box 12, Folder 181)
      - Passport
        See: Accession 2004-M-056, 1916-2003 Box 19
  - Printed materials and clippings [including blank postcards], 1943-1944, 1968, 1972, 1987-2002, undated (Box 13, Folder 182 - 186)
  - Topical
    - AIDS [clippings], 1991, undated (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - American Civil Liberties Union [documents regarding a conference on the Cold War], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 188)